[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "Dhaka is becoming one of the _ cities in Asia.",
    "options": ["more busy", "busy", "busiest", "most busiest"],
    "answer": "busiest"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "He had written the book before he ---.",
    "options": ["will be retired", "has retired", "had retired", "retired"],
    "answer": "retired"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "Rizvi requested Rini _ telephone to attend the meeting.",
    "options": ["to ages", "from ages", "for ages", "since ages"],
    "answer": "from ages"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "The word 'precedence' means-",
    "options": ["example", "elderly", "case", "priority"],
    "answer": "priority"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "The price of rice are _.",
    "options": ["risen", "Raising", "rising", "raised"],
    "answer": "Raising"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "To get along with means-----",
    "options": ["to accompany", "to adjust", "to interest", "to walk"],
    "answer": "to adjust"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "\"\"\"If winter comes, can spring be far behind?\"\" These lines were written by _.\"",
    "options": ["Shelley", "Eliot", "Forst", "Keats"],
    "answer": "Shelley"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "The verb of the word 'short' is _.",
    "options": ["shorten", "Enshort", "shorted", "shorting"],
    "answer": "shorten"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "'Light' is to 'dark' as 'cold' is to _.",
    "options": ["cool", "winter", "heat", "Hot"],
    "answer": "Hot"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "Many prefer donating money ..... distributing clothes.",
    "options": ["but", "to", "Than", "without"],
    "answer": "to"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "Julia has been ill _three months.",
    "options": ["about", "in", "for", "Since"],
    "answer": "for"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "We were waiting for the bus. The underlined part is.",
    "options": [
      "a verb phrase",
      "a prepositional phrase",
      "an infinitive",
      "a noun phrase"
    ],
    "answer": "a noun phrase"
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "The word 'disinterested' means",
    "options": ["lack of interest", "indifferent", "callous", "neutral"],
    "answer": "neutral"
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "Who did write first English dictionary ?",
    "options": ["Samuel Johnson", "Ben Jonson", "Boswell", "Milton"],
    "answer": "Samuel Johnson"
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "New programs will be _ next week in Bangladesh Television.",
    "options": ["published", "telecasted", "Telecast", "broadcasted"],
    "answer": "Telecast"
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "The word 'electorate' means :",
    "options": [
      "election office",
      "a body of voter",
      "many elections",
      "candidates"
    ],
    "answer": "a body of voter"
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "'Animal Farm' was written by-",
    "options": ["George Orwel", "Stevenson", "Swift", "Mark Twain"],
    "answer": "George Orwel"
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "There is no alternative _training.",
    "options": ["than", "of", "for", "To"],
    "answer": "of"
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "Which sentence is correct ?",
    "options": [
      "This is a unique case",
      "This is an unique case",
      "This is a very unique case",
      "This is the most unique case"
    ],
    "answer": "This is a unique case"
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "I cannot _to pay such high prices.",
    "options": ["afford", "try", "but", "Able"],
    "answer": "afford"
  }
]
